We've talked about neural networks in previous courses and modules,
すでにニューラルネットワークは 説明しましたが
but now, let's learn some of the science behind them.
ここではその技術を説明します
We recently saw that feature crosses did very well in a problem like this.
このような問題で特徴クロスが役立つことが わかってきました
If x1 is the horizontal dimension,
x1が水平寸法で
and x2 is the vertical dimension,
x2が垂直寸法の場合
there was no linear combination of the two features to describe this distribution.
この分布を示す2つの特徴の 線形組み合わせはありませんでした
It wasn't until we did some feature engineering and crossed x1 and x2 to get
特徴エンジニアリングを行って x1とx2を交差させるまで
a new feature x3 which equals
新しい特徴x3を得られませんでした
x1 times x2 where we are able to describe our data distribution.
x3はx1掛けるx2と同じで このデータ分布を示せます
So, manual handcraft to feature
手動による特徴エンジニアリングで
engineering can easily solve all of our nonlinear problems.
非線形問題はすべて簡単に解決できます
Right? Unfortunately, the real world
ですよね？残念ながら現実世界では
almost never has such easily described distributions.
こんなに簡単に分布を描けません
So, feature engineering, even after years the brightest people working on it,
特徴エンジニアリングは 天才たちが何年研究しても
can only get so far.
これが限界です
For instance, what feature crosses would you need to model this distribution?
たとえばこの分布のモデル化には どんな特徴クロスが必要ですか
It looks like two circles over top of each other or maybe two spirals,
2つの円が重なっているようにも 2つのらせんにも見えますが
but whatever it is, it's very messy.
とにかく非常に乱雑です
This example sets up the usefulness of neural networks so they can
この例はニューラルネットワーク（NN）の 有用性を示します
algorithmically create very complex feature crosses and transformations.
NNはアルゴリズムで複雑な特徴クロスと 変換を作成できます
You can imagine much more complicated spaces that
このらせんよりはるかに複雑な空間では
even this spiral that really necessitate the use of neural networks.
NNの使用が必須です
Neural networks can help as an alternative to feature crossing by combining features.
NNは特徴を組み合わせて 特徴クロスの代用として機能します
When we were designing our neural network architecture we want to
NNのアーキテクチャの設計で目指すのは
structure the model in such a way that there are features combined.
特徴の組み合わせが存在するような モデルの構築です
Then we want to add another layer to combine our combinations
次に他の層を追加して 既存の組み合わせに重ね
and then add another layer to combine those combinations and so on.
さらに層を追加して既存の組み合わせに 重ねていきます
How do we choose the right combinations of
どうすれば特徴などの
our features and the combinations of those etc?
正しい組み合わせを選択できますか？
You get the model to learn them through training of course.
もちろんトレーニングでモデルに 学習させるのです
This is the basic intuition behind neural nets.
これがニューラルネットの基本知識です
This approach isn't necessarily better than feature crosses,
特徴クロスより優れているわけではありませんが
but is a flexible alternative that works well in many cases.
多くのケースで役立つ柔軟な代替方法です
Here is a graphical representation of a linear model.
この図は線形モデルを表しています
We have three inputs x1,
3つの入力
They're combined with some weight given on each edge to produce an output.
各エッジに重み与えて組み合わせを行い 出力を生成します
They're often is an extra biased term,
別の偏り項もありますが
but for simplicity it isn't shown here.
簡単にするため表示していません
This is a linear model since is a form of y equals w1 times x1,
これは線形モデルです y = w1 x x1
plus w2 times x2,
+ w2 x x2
plus w3 times x3.
+ w3 x x3です
Now, let's add a hidden layer to our network of nodes and edges.
ここでノードとエッジのネットワークに 隠れ層を追加します
Our input layer has three nodes and our hidden layer also has three.
入力層にも隠れ層にもノードが3つあります
But now, hidden nodes.
ここでは隠れノードを見ます
Since this is a completely connected layer,
これは完全につながった層なので
there are three times three edges or nine weights.
エッジが3 x 3で重みが9になります
Surely, this is a nonlinear model now that we can
確かにこれは非線形モデルなので
use to solve our nonlinear problems, right?
非線形問題の解決に使えますよね？
Unfortunately, not. Let's break it down.
残念ながら使えません 詳細に見ていきましょう
The input to the first hidden node is the weighted sum of w1 times x1,
最初の隠れノードへの入力はw1 x x1
plus w4 times x2,
+ w4 x x2
plus w7 times x3.
+ w7 x x3の加重和です
The input to the second hidden node is the weighted sum w2 times
2番目の隠れノードへの入力はw2 x x1
x1 plus w5 times x2 plus w8 times x3.
+ w5 x x2 + w8 x x3の 加重和です
The input to the third hidden node is the weighted sum w3
3番目の隠れノードへの入力はw3 x x1
Combining it all together at the output node,
すべてを出力ノードで組み合わせると
we have w10 times h1,
w10 x h1
plus w11 times h2,
+ w11 x h2
plus w12 times h3.
+ w12 x h3になります
Remember though, that h1,
説明したようにh1
h2 and h3 are just linear combinations of the input features.
h2とh3は入力特徴の線形の組み合わせに すぎません
Therefore, expanding it out,
そのためこれを展開すると
we're left with a complex set of weight constants multiplied by
一連の複雑な重み定数に各入力値
each input value x1, x2, and x3.
x1 x2 x3を掛けたものが残ります
We can substitute each couple of weights for a new weight.
各組の重みを新しい重みに代入できます
Look familiar?
見覚えがあるでしょう？
This is exactly the same linear model as before
隠れ層を追加する前の線形モデルと
despite adding a hidden layer of neurons. So, what happened?
まったく同じです なぜでしょうか？
What if we added another hidden layer?
隠れ層をもっと追加したら？
Unfortunately, this once again and collapses all the way back down
残念ながらこれも集約され
into a single weight matrix multiplied by each of the three inputs.
3つの各入力を掛けた1つの重み行列になります
It is the same linear model.
同じ線形モデルです
We can continue this process add infinitum and it would still be the same result,
このプロセスを無限に続けても 同じ結果になります
albeit a lot more costly computationally for training or prediction for a much,
莫大な計算コストをかけて 複雑なアーキテクチャのトレーニングや
much more complicated architecture than needed.
予測を行っても同じです
Thinking about this from a linear algebra perspective,
これを線形代数的観点から見ると
you're multiplying multiple matrices together in a chain.
複数の行列が1つの連鎖で掛けられています
In this small example,
この小さな例では
I first multiply a three by three matrix,
まず3x3の行列を掛け
the transpose of the weight matrix between the input layer and a hidden layer one,
入力層と隠れ層1間の重み行列の転置を
by the three by one input vector resulting in the three by
3x1の入力ベクトルで行うことにより
one vector which are the values at each hidden neuron in the hidden layer one.
3x1ベクトルが隠れ層1の各隠れニューロンの 値になります
Define their second hidden layers neuron's values,
2番目の隠れ層のニューロンの値を定義して
I multiplied the transpose of it's
3x3の重み行列の
three by three weight matrix that connects hidden layer
転置行列を掛けて隠れ層1を
one with hidden layer two to my resultant vector at hidden layer one.
隠れ層2につなげると それが隠れ層1の結果のベクトルになります
As you can guess, the two,
おわかりのように
three by three weight matrices can be combined into on,
2つの3x3の重み行列が
three by thre matrix by first calculating
1つの3x3行列になります
This still gives the same shape for h2,
これでも2番目の隠れ層のニューロンの
the second hidden layer neuron's value vector.
値のベクトルh2の形は同じです
Adding in the final layer between hidden layer two and the output layer,
隠れ層2と出力層の間に最後の層を追加するには
I need to multiply the preceding steps by
前の手順に先ほどの2つの層の間の
the transpose of the weight matrix between the last two layers.
重み行列の転置行列を掛ける必要があります
Even though when feeding forward through a neural network you perform
NNによるフィードフォーワードでも
the matrix multiplication from right to left by applying it from left to right,
行列の積を右から左に行うには 左から右に適用します
you can see that our large chain of
この行列要素の大きな連鎖が
matrix complications collapses down into just a three valued vector.
値が3つだけのベクトルに集約されました
If you train this model in just a simple linear regression case of
3つの重みが並んだ単回帰ケースで
three weight side by side and they both fall into the same minimum on the low surface,
このモデルをトレーニングし どちらも最終面で同じ極小値に集約されるなら
than even though I did a ton of computation to calculate all 21 weights
膨大な演算で21の重みすべてを計算しても
my matrix product chain will condense down into the lower equation,
この行列積の連鎖は低次方程式に集約され
the weight will exactly match the training simple linear regressions weights.
重みはトレーニング中の単回帰の重みと まったく同じになります
All of the work for the same result.
すべての作業が同じ結果になります
You're probably thinking now, "Hey,
皆様はこう思うでしょう
I thought neural networks are all about adding layers upon layers in neurons.
「NNとはニューロンに層を追加することだ
How can I do deep learning when all of my layers collapse into just one?"
全層が1つに集約されるなら ディープラーニングなんてできない」
I've got good news for you.
朗報があります
There is an easy solution.
簡単な解決策があります
The solution is adding a non-linear transformation layer which is facilitated by
それは非線形変換層を追加することで
And thinking of terms of the graph such as you're making TensorFlow,
TensorFlowなどのグラフの場合は
you can imagine each neuron actually having two nodes.
各ニューロンに2つのノードがあると 考えてください
The first node being the result of the weighted sum wx plus b,
最初のノードは加重和wx + bの結果で
and the second node being the result
2つ目のノードは
of that being passed through the activation function.
活性化関数を通過した結果です
In other words, there are inputs of
つまり 活性化関数の入力の後に
so the activation function acts as the transition point between.
活性化関数が間の転移点として機能します
Adding in this non-linear transformation is the only way
この非線形転換の追加が
Even if you have a layer with nonlinear activation of functions your network,
ネットワークに非線形活性化関数の層が 1つあっても
if elsewhere in the network you have two or more layers with linear activation functions,
ネットワークのどこかに線形活性化関数が 2つ以上あると
those can still be collapsed into just one network.
1つのネットワークに集約されます
Usually, neural networks have all layers
通常NNでは
nonlinear for the first and minus one layers and then have
最初とマイナス1の層は非線形の層で
the final layer transformation be linear for regression or
最終層の変換は回帰またはシグモイド
sigmoid or softmax which we'll talk about soon for classification.
ソフトマックスの線形になります
It all depends on what you want the output to be.
すべては必要とする出力によって変わります
Thinking about this again from
これをもう一度線形代数の観点から考えると
we are multiplying a matrix or vector to it leading to our desired shape and result.
行列またはベクトルを掛け合わせて 目的の形状や結果になるようにします
Such as when I want to scale a matrix,
行列のサイズ変更と同様に
I can multiply it by a constant.
定数を掛けることができます
But truly, what you are doing is multiplying it by an identity matrix,
しかし実際は単位行列を掛けています
multiplied by that constant.
その定数を掛けます
So, it is a diagonal matrix with that constant all on the diagonal.
そのためこれは全対角が定数の対角行列です
This would be collapsed into just a matrix product.
これは単なる行列積に集約されます
However, if I add a non-linearity,
しかし非線形性を追加すると
what I am doing is not able to be represented by a matrix.
行列で表せなくなります
Since, I am element y it's applying a function into my input.
要素yで関数を入力に適用しているためです
For instance, if I have
たとえば
I'm applying a function of the product of
最初の隠れ層の重み行列と
the transpose of my first hidden layers weight matrix and my input vector.
入力ベクトルの置換の積の関数を適用します
The lower equation is my activation function in a ReLU.
低次方程式はReLUの活性化関数です
Since I cannot represent the transformation in terms of linear algebra,
線形代数では変換を表せないので
I can no longer collapse that portion of my transformation chain
変換連鎖のその部分はこれ以上集約できず
thus complexity to my model remains and
モデルの複雑性は変わらず
doesn't collapse into just one linear combination of the inputs.
入力の線形結合に集約されません
Note that I can still collapse second hidden layer of weight matrix and
重み行列の2番目の隠れ層と出力層の重み行列は
the output layer weight matrix since there is no nonlinear function being applied here.
まだ非線形関数を適用していないので 集約されます
This means that whenever there are two or more linear layers consecutively,
つまり線形層が2つ以上連続している場合
they can always be collapsed back into one layer no matter how many they are.
それが何層でも1つの層に集約されます
Therefore, they have the most complex functions being created by your network,
そのため最も複雑な関数が ネットワークで作成されています
it's best to have your entire network have a linear activation functions,
ネットワーク全体に線形活性化関数を入れるのが 最適ですが
except at the last layer in case you might use a different type of output at the end.
最後に異なるタイプの出力を使用する場合は 最後の層を除外します
Why is it important adding non-linear activation functions to neural networks?
NNに非線形活性化関数を追加することが 重要な理由は？
The correct answer is because it stops the layers
正解は複数の層が線形モデルに
from collapsing back into just a linear model.
集約されないようにするためです
Not only do nonlinear activation functions help
非線形活性化関数は
but it allows for deep compositional functions.
深層合成関数も可能にします
As we explained, if there are any two or more layers with linear activation functions,
説明したように 線形活性化関数に2つ以上の層がある場合
this product of matrices can be summarized by
この行列の積は
Therefore, you end up with slower model with
そのため演算は多いのに
more computation but with all of your functional complexity reduced.
機能的複雑性がすべて排除された 低速モデルになります
Non-linearities do not add regularization to
非線形性は損失関数に正則性を追加せず
the loss function and they do not invoke early stopping.
早期中止を呼び出しません
Even though nonlinear activation functions do
非線形活性化関数がデータ空間に
create complex transformations in the vector space,
複素変換を作成したとしても
that dimension does not change it remains the same vector space.
次元は変化せず 同一ベクトル空間に留まります
Albeit stretched, squished or rotated.
ただし圧迫や拡大、回転はあります
As mentioned in one of our previous courses,
前のコースでも触れたように
there are many nonlinear activation functions with sigmoid,
シグモイドには多数の非線形活性化関数があり
and the scaled and shifted sigmoid,
スケール／シフトシグモイドと
hyperbolic tangent being some of the earliest.
双曲正接は最も古いものです
However, as mentioned before,
ただしすでに述べたように
these can have saturation which leads to the vanishing gradient problem,
これは飽和状態から勾配消失問題につながります
where with zero gradients,
ゼロ勾配では
the models weights don't update and training halts.
モデルの重みは更新されず トレーニングは停止します
The Rectified Linear Unit or ReLU for short is one of
Rectified Linear Unit（ReLU）は
our favorites because it's simple and works well.
簡単でうまく機能するためよく使用されます
In the positive domain it is linear,
正領域では線形なので飽和状態になりませんが
Networks with ReLU hidden activation,
隠れ活性化にReLUを使うネットワークは
often have 10 times the speed of training than networks with sigmoid, hidden activations.
隠れ活性化にシグモイドを使うネットワークと 比べてトレーニング速度が10倍です
However, due to negative domains function always being zero,
ただし負領域では関数が常に0なので
we can end up with the real layers dying.
実層は消失して終わります
What I mean by this is that,
これが示しているのは
when you start getting inputs in
入力を負領域で開始して
the negative domain and the output of the activation will be zero,
活性化の出力がゼロになると
which doesn't help in the next layer and given inputs in the positive domain.
次の層と正領域での入力に役立たない ということです
This compounds and creates a lot of zero activations,
これにより多数のゼロ活性化が作成されます
during back propagation when updating the weights since
重みを更新する誤差逆伝搬中に
we have to multiply our errors derivative by their activation,
誤差導関数に活性化を掛ける必要があるため
we end up with a gradient of zero.
勾配ゼロで終わります
Thus, a weight of data zero and thus the weights
このようにデータゼロの重みは変化せず
Fortunately, a lot of clever methods have been developed to
幸運にも 巧妙な方法が多数開発されており
slightly modify the ReLU to ensure training doesn't stall,
トレーニングが停止しないよう ReLUを少し変更しながらも
but still, with bunch of the benefits of the vanilla ReLU.
一般的なReLUのメリットを維持しています
Here again is the vanilla ReLu,
一般的なReLUに戻ります
the maximum operator can also be represented by the piecewise linear equation,
maximum演算子は区分線形式で 表すこともできます
where less than zero, function is zero.
ここではゼロ未満で 関数はゼロです
And greater than or equal to zero, the function is X.
またゼロ以上で関数はXです
A smooth approximation of the ReLUs function
ReLU関数の平滑近似は
is the analytic function of the natural log of one,
1の自然対数の解析関数と
plus the exponential X.
指数関数Xを足したものです
This is called the Softplus function.
これをソフトプラス関数と言います
Interestingly, the derivative the Softplus function is a logistic function.
ソフトプラス関数の導関数は ロジスティック関数です
The pros of using the Softplus function are,
ソフトプラス関数を使用するメリットは
it's continuous and differentiable at zero,
ReLU関数と異なり
unlike the ReLu function.
0でも連続かつ微分可能です
However, due to the natural log and exponential,
ただし自然対数と指数関数により
there's added computation compared to ReLUs,
ReLUと比べて追加の計算があるため
and ReLUs still have as good of results in practice.
実際にはReLUの結果も同様に良好です
Therefore, Softplus is usually discouraged to be using deep learning.
そのためソフトプラスはディープラーニング での使用は推奨されません
To try and solve our issue of dying ReLUs due to zero activations,
ゼロ活性化によるdying ReLUの問題を 解決するため
the Leaky ReLU was developed.
Leaky ReLUが開発されました
Just like ReLUs, Leaky ReLUs have a piecewise linear function.
ReLU同様 区分線形関数があります
However, in the negative domain,
ただし負領域には
rather than zero, they have a non-zero slope specifically, 0.01.
0ではなく 厳密に言えば0.01の 非ゼロ勾配があります
This way, when the unit is not activated,
このようにユニットが活性化していなくても
Leaky ReLUs still allow a small non-zero gradient to pass through them,
Leaky ReLUではわずかな非ゼロ勾配で それらを通過できるため
which hopefully will allow weight updating and training to continue.
重みの更新やトレーニングの継続ができると 考えられます
Taking this Leaky idea one step further is the parametric ReLU or PReLU for short.
このLeakyの考え方を一歩先に進めたのが Parametric ReLU（PReLU）です
Here, rather than arbitrarily allowing
これは負領域でXを0.01として
one hundredth of an X through in the negative domain,
任意で通過させるのではなく
it lets Alpha of X through.
Xをαとして通過させます
But, what is the parameter Alpha supposed to be?
しかしパラメータαはどうなるべきですか？
In the graph, I set Alpha to be 0.5 for visualization purposes.
グラフでは可視化するために αを0.5に設定しました
But in practice, it is actually a learned parameter
しかし実際には他のNNパラメータとともに
from training along with the other neural network parameters.
トレーニングから得た学習済みパラメータです
This way, rather than us setting this value,
このようにこの値は設定するのではなく
the value will be determined during training via the data and should
データを使ったトレーニング中に決定され
learn a more optimal value than we our priority could set.
優先順位で設定するより適した値を学習します
Notice that when Alpha is less than one,
αが0未満の場合
the formula can be rewritten back into the compact form using the maximum.
式はmaximumを使ってコンパクトフォームに 書き直せます
Specifically, the max of X or alpha times x.
具体的にはmaxはXまたはαxです
There are also randomized Leaky ReLUs where instead of Alpha being trained,
ランダム化したLeaky ReLUもあり これではαをトレーニングするのではなく
it is a sampled from a uniform distribution randomly.
一様分布からランダムにサンプルを抽出します
This can have an effect similar to drop out since you
厳密には各α値のネットワークは異なるため
technically have a different network for each value of Alpha.
これには脱落と類似した効果があります
And therefore, it is making something similar to an ensemble.
そのため集合と類似したものが形成されます
At test time, all the values of Alpha are
テスト時にすべてのα値は
averaged together to a deterministic value to use for predictions.
予測に使用する目的で 決定論的値に平均化されます
There is also the ReLU6 variant,
ReLU6という変種もあります
this is another piecewise linear function with three segments.
これも区分線形関数で線分が3本あります
Like a normal ReLU,
通常のReLU同様
it is zero in the negative domain,
負領域では0ですが
however the positive domain the ReLU6 is kept at six.
正領域ではReLU6は6のままです
You're probably thinking, "Why is it kept at six?
「なぜ6のままなのか？」と思うでしょう
You can imagine one of these ReLU units having only
これらのReLUユニットの1つは
six replicated by a shifted bernoulli units,
シフトベルヌーイユニットによって複製された 6のみを持ちます
rather than an infinite amount due to the hard cap.
ハードキャップの場合は膨大な量になります
In general, these are called the ReLU n units,
通常これらはReLU nユニットと呼ばれます
where n is the cap value.
ここでnはキャップ値です
In testing, six was found to be the most optimal value.
テストで6が最適値であるとわかりました
ReLU6 units can help models learn sparse features sooner.
ReLU6ユニットではモデルはスパース性を より早く学習できます
They were first used convolutional deep elite networks on a CIFAR-10 image data set.
まずCIFAR-10画像データセットの畳込み 深層エリートネットワークで使われました
They also have useful property of preparing
ネットワーク準備に有用なプロパティもあり 推論用の正確な固定小数点を得られます
If the upper limit is unbounded,
上限が有界でない場合
then you lose too many bits to the Q part of a fixed point number,
固定小数点数のQ部分で多数のビットを失い
whereas with an upper limit of six,
上限が6の場合は
it leaves enough bits to the fractional part of
数値の端数部分に十分なビットが残り
the number making it represented well enough to do good inference.
十分な数値を示し適切な推論を行えます
Lastly, there is the exponential linear unit or ELU.
最後は指数線形ユニット（ELU）です
It is approximately linear in the non-negative portion of the input space and is smooth,
入力空間の非負領域ではほぼ線形です
monotonic and most importantly,
入力の負領域では平坦かつ単調で
non-zero in the negative portion of the input.
最も重要なことですが非ゼロでです
They are also better zero centered than vanilla ReLUs which can speed up learning.
また通常のReLUよりゼロ中心なので 学習が高速化します
The main drawback of ELUs are that they are more compositionally
ELUの主な欠点は指数関数を計算する 必要があるため
expensive than ReLUs due to having to calculate the exponential.
ReLUより組成的に高価なことです
Neural networks can be arbitrarily complex,
NNは任意に複雑になる可能性があります
there can be many layers,
多くの層や
neurons per layer, outputs, inputs,
層ごとのニューロン、出力、入力
different types activation functions et cetra.
さまざまな種類の活性化関数などがあります
What does the purpose of multiple layers?
複数層の目的は何でしょうか？
Each layer I add,
層を追加するごとに
adds the complexity of the functions I can create.
作成できる関数の複雑性が追加されます
Each subsequent layer is a composition of the previous functions.
以降の各層は前の関数の合成です
Since we are using nonlinear activation functions in my hidden layers,
隠れ層では非線形活性化関数を使用しているので
I'm creating a stack of data transformations that rotate,
データを回転、拡張、圧迫する
stretch and squeeze my data.
大量のデータ変換を作成しています
Remember, the purpose of doing all of this is
こうしたことを行う目的は
to transfer my data in such a way that can nicely
超平面をデータに合わせて回帰させる方法か
fit hyper plane to it for regression or
超平面でデータを分離して分類する方法により
separate my data with a hyper planes for classification.
データを転送することです
We are mapping from the original feature space to some new convoluted feature space.
元の特徴空間から新しい複雑な特徴空間に マッピングしています
What does adding additional neurons to a layer do?
ニューロンを層に追加するとどうなるのか？
Each neuron I add, adds a new dimension to my vector space.
ニューロンを追加するごとに 新しい次元がベクトル空間に追加されます
If I begin with three input neurons,
3つの入力ニューロンで開始する場合は
I start in R3 vector space.
R3ベクトル空間で始めます
But if my next layer has four neurons that I moved to an R4 vector space.
しかし次の層にはR4ベクトル空間に移動した 4つのニューロンがあります
Back when we talked about Kernel methods in our previous course,
前のコースでカーネル法を説明したとき
we had a data set that couldn't be easily separated
超平面で簡単に分離できないデータセットが
with a hyper plane in the original input vector space.
元の入力ベクトル空間にありました
But, by adding the dimension and then transform
しかし次元を追加して 新しい次元が埋まるように
the data to fill that new dimension in just the right way,
理にかなった方法でデータを変換することで
we were then easily able to make a clean slice between the classes of data.
データクラス間に明確なスライスを 簡単に作成できるようになりました
The same applies here with neural networks.
同じことをここでNNに適用します
What might having multiple output nodes do?
複数の出力ノードがあるとどうなるでしょうか？
Having multiple output nodes allows you to
複数の出力ノードがあると
compare to multiple labels and then propagate the corresponding areas backwards.
複数のラベルを比較して対応する領域を 後方へ伝搬できます
You can imagine doing image classification where there are
各画像内に複数のエンテイティまたはクラスが ある場合に
multiple entities or classes within each image.
画像分類を行うようなものです
We can't just predict one class because there maybe many,
クラスは多数あるので 1つのクラスの予測はできません
so having this flexibility is great.
そのためこの柔軟性は役立ちます
Neural networks should be arbitrarily complex.
NNは任意に複雑でなければなりません
To increase hidden dimensions,
隠れ次元を増やすために
I can add blank.
＿＿＿を追加できます
To increase function composition,
関数合成を増やすには
If I have multiple labels for example,
たとえば複数のラベルがあると
I can add blank.
＿＿＿を追加できます
The correct answer is neuron's, layers, outputs.
正解は、ニューロン、層、出力です
To change hidden dimensions, I can change the layers number of neurons.
隠れ次元を変更するために ニューロンの層の数を変更できます
So that determines the dimensions of the vector space like intermediate vector is in.
そのため中間ベクトルが入るような ベクトル空間の次元を決定します
If a layer has four neurons,
層に4つのニューロンがあれば
than it is in our four vector space,
それは4ベクトル空間にあります
and if a layer has 500 neurons it is in R 500 vector space.
層に500個のニューロンがあれば それは500ベクトル空間にあります
Meaning, it has 500 real dimensions.
つまり実次元が500あるという意味です
Adding a layer doesn't change the dimension of the previous layer and it might not even
層を追加しても前の層の次元は変わらず
change the dimension in its layer
ニューロンの数が前の層と異ならなければ
unless it has a different number of neurons in the previous layer.
その層の次元さえも変わりません
What additional layers do add is a greater composition of functions.
層を追加することで関数合成が向上します
Remember, Go of F of X,
Go of F of Xは
is the composition of the function G with the function F on the input X.
入力Xでの関数Gと関数Fの合成です
Therefore, I first transform X by F and then
したがって まずXをFで変換して
transform that result by G. The more layers I have,
次にその結果をGで変換します
This is great for combining non-linear functions together to make
これは非線形関数を組み合わせて
very convoluted feature maps that are hard for
複雑な特徴マップを作るのに適しています
humans to construct but great for computers,
これは人間よりコンピュータが得意なことです
and allow us to better get our data into
私たちはデータを整形して
a shape that we can learn and gain insights from.
そこから洞察を得ることができます
Speaking of insights, we receive those through our output layers,
洞察は出力層から受け取ります
where during inference, those will be the answers to our ML formulated problem.
推測中 洞察がMLによって明確化された 問題への答えになります
If you only want to know the probability of an image being a dog,
画像が犬になる確率を知りたいだけなら
then you can get by with only one output node.
出力ノードが1つあれば十分ですが
But if he wanted to know the probability of an image being a cat, dog,
画像が猫、犬、鳥、ネズミになる 確率を知りたければ
then you would need to have a node for each one.
それぞれに1つずつのノードが必要になります
The other three answers are all wrong since they get two or more of the words wrong.
他の3つの答えはすべて間違いです 2つ以上の用語が間違っています